{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946858643027","data":{"timestamp":" 946858643027"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_031643"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946858696505","data":{"timestamp":" 946858696505"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_031643"," gameId":" bc7fb875-754c-4391-821a-1764cc5058e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pamoja_hadithi-kubwa-yule-pamoja"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" pamoja"," userResponse":" pamoja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946858741065","data":{"timestamp":" 946858741065"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_031643"," gameId":" bc7fb875-754c-4391-821a-1764cc5058e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kucha_kuzaliwa-tambarare-kucha-njema"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kucha"," userResponse":" tambarare"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946858743751","data":{"timestamp":" 946858743751"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_031643"," gameId":" bc7fb875-754c-4391-821a-1764cc5058e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kucha_kuzaliwa-tambarare-kucha-njema"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kucha"," userResponse":" kuzaliwa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946858746420","data":{"timestamp":" 946858746420"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_031643"," gameId":" bc7fb875-754c-4391-821a-1764cc5058e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kucha_kuzaliwa-tambarare-kucha-njema"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kucha"," userResponse":" njema"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946858749107","data":{"timestamp":" 946858749107"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_031643"," gameId":" bc7fb875-754c-4391-821a-1764cc5058e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kucha_kuzaliwa-tambarare-kucha-njema"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kucha"," userResponse":" kucha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946858775790","data":{"timestamp":" 946858775790"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_031643"," gameId":" bc7fb875-754c-4391-821a-1764cc5058e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" usiku_usiku-wapi-mti-kubwa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" usiku"," userResponse":" kubwa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946858778464","data":{"timestamp":" 946858778464"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_031643"," gameId":" bc7fb875-754c-4391-821a-1764cc5058e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" usiku_usiku-wapi-mti-kubwa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" usiku"," userResponse":" usiku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946858842910","data":{"timestamp":" 946858842910"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_031643"," gameId":" bc7fb875-754c-4391-821a-1764cc5058e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" usiku_usiku-wapi-mti-kubwa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946858842993","data":{"timestamp":" 946858842993"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_031643"," gameId":" bc7fb875-754c-4391-821a-1764cc5058e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unafikiri nini kilichotokea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOTOKEA"," userResponse":" KILICHOTOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946858854499","data":{"timestamp":" 946858854498"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_031643"," gameId":" ff95f8e5-37b6-4e25-b46a-fa4fb98203ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946858854880","data":{"timestamp":" 946858854879"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_031643"," gameId":" ff95f8e5-37b6-4e25-b46a-fa4fb98203ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946858855374","data":{"timestamp":" 946858855373"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_031643"," gameId":" ff95f8e5-37b6-4e25-b46a-fa4fb98203ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946858855730","data":{"timestamp":" 946858855729"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_031643"," gameId":" ff95f8e5-37b6-4e25-b46a-fa4fb98203ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946858856145","data":{"timestamp":" 946858856144"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_031643"," gameId":" ff95f8e5-37b6-4e25-b46a-fa4fb98203ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946858856632","data":{"timestamp":" 946858856631"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_031643"," gameId":" ff95f8e5-37b6-4e25-b46a-fa4fb98203ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946858856865","data":{"timestamp":" 946858856864"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_031643"," gameId":" ff95f8e5-37b6-4e25-b46a-fa4fb98203ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946858860038","data":{"timestamp":" 946858860037"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_031643"," gameId":" ff95f8e5-37b6-4e25-b46a-fa4fb98203ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946858860072","data":{"timestamp":" 946858860072"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_031643"," gameId":" ff95f8e5-37b6-4e25-b46a-fa4fb98203ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946858860797","data":{"timestamp":" 946858860796"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_031643"," gameId":" ff95f8e5-37b6-4e25-b46a-fa4fb98203ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946858861202","data":{"timestamp":" 946858861202"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_031643"," gameId":" ff95f8e5-37b6-4e25-b46a-fa4fb98203ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946858861501","data":{"timestamp":" 946858861501"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_031643"," gameId":" ff95f8e5-37b6-4e25-b46a-fa4fb98203ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946858861717","data":{"timestamp":" 946858861717"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_031643"," gameId":" ff95f8e5-37b6-4e25-b46a-fa4fb98203ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946858861922","data":{"timestamp":" 946858861921"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_031643"," gameId":" ff95f8e5-37b6-4e25-b46a-fa4fb98203ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946858862248","data":{"timestamp":" 946858862247"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_031643"," gameId":" ff95f8e5-37b6-4e25-b46a-fa4fb98203ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946858862486","data":{"timestamp":" 946858862486"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_031643"," gameId":" ff95f8e5-37b6-4e25-b46a-fa4fb98203ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946858865146","data":{"timestamp":" 946858865146"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_031643"," gameId":" ff95f8e5-37b6-4e25-b46a-fa4fb98203ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946858865224","data":{"timestamp":" 946858865224"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_031643"," gameId":" ff95f8e5-37b6-4e25-b46a-fa4fb98203ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946858876784","data":{"timestamp":" 946858876784"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_031643"," gameId":" d80018cf-2c18-4dc4-a66f-4aba2f0cb4a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-4-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946858883329","data":{"timestamp":" 946858883329"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_031643"," gameId":" d80018cf-2c18-4dc4-a66f-4aba2f0cb4a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_2-8-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946858890523","data":{"timestamp":" 946858890523"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_031643"," gameId":" d80018cf-2c18-4dc4-a66f-4aba2f0cb4a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_5-7-1"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946858898412","data":{"timestamp":" 946858898412"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_031643"," gameId":" d80018cf-2c18-4dc4-a66f-4aba2f0cb4a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2q.AV.rise.26"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_7_5-7-1"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}